<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rant-and-ramble on bananafish</title>
    <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/tags/rant-and-ramble/</link>
    <description>Recent content in rant-and-ramble on bananafish</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-NZ</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 01:48:57 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://le-bananafish.github.io/tags/rant-and-ramble/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>April 2021</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/april-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 01:48:57 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/april-2021/</guid>
      <description>Maintenance and Learning&amp;nbsp;¶ There are so many things that I was gonna write. But I got lazy and I got annoyed at how little I understand how Hugo, the software I use to generate this site, works. I would love to be able to create Table(s) of Contents, or add templates for things like signatures, or dynamically alter the font of the theme, but I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to do any of that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Haven&#39;t Been Writing</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/i-havent-been-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 12:31:50 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/i-havent-been-writing/</guid>
      <description>In the middle of January 2021 with nothing else to do, I made myself a New Years resolution. I vowed to write &amp;ldquo;once a week, or at the bare minimum, once a month&amp;rdquo;. I had a good run for three weeks in which I wrote a post roughly once a week. Then February hit, I procrastinated even more and the realisation that uni was looming sapped my willpower. So I amended my resolution to &amp;ldquo;once a fortnight&amp;rdquo; and wrote a single post in the entire month of February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Price of Wisdom</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/the-price-of-wisdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 15:05:10 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/the-price-of-wisdom/</guid>
      <description>Goodbye, oh teeth of wisdom!&amp;nbsp;¶ So.., I had my wisdom teeth extracted. They caused more trouble than they were worth. One was growing into the tooth next to it whilst another failed to erupt and was stuck under the gum. My teeth were biting into the gums.&#xA;The biggest irony is that the tooth that should&amp;rsquo;ve caused trouble was perfectly fine and the one that should&amp;rsquo;ve been fine was causing infections and swelling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Site Who This</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/new-site-who-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 21:37:43 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/new-site-who-this/</guid>
      <description>Secret Hidden Level 1 Header&amp;nbsp;¶ This is my first post. Enjoy!&#xA;Part 1: Joke&amp;rsquo;s on you&amp;nbsp;¶ Joke&amp;rsquo;s on you, this isn&amp;rsquo;t my first rodeo with static site generators and as an experienced beginner level experimenter, I have a few complaints about static site generators.&#xA;I mean, why not have your first post be a complaint?&#xA;First, some history.&#xA;So, at one point in time at some point in time last year (2017) or so, I read somewhere that it was a great idea to showcase yourself by having a personal website as like a part-CV part experience point of reference.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
