<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>site/update on bananafish</title>
    <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/tags/site/update/</link>
    <description>Recent content in site/update on bananafish</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://le-bananafish.github.io/tags/site/update/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>November 2021</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/november-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 18:55:05 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/november-2021/</guid>
      <description>Preamble Isn&amp;rsquo;t ironic when you&amp;rsquo;re busy, you yearn for free time, but when you have lots of free time, you&amp;rsquo;re bored out of your mind?
No, just me?
November Update So, you may have noticed that my last post was in July; before that, the last post was in April. I managed to write enough to scrape by for the first four months.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a long year and I&amp;rsquo;ve forgotten most things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2021</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/july-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 02:27:39 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/july-2021/</guid>
      <description>The last post I made was in April.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to make an excuse; it&amp;rsquo;s a valid excuse. When May and June came around, so did all the assignments and coursework, and I was simply swamped by it all.
However, what&amp;rsquo;s not valid is using it not to work on my &amp;ldquo;projects&amp;rdquo;. They haven&amp;rsquo;t seen any progress in months (or years). For that reason, I&amp;rsquo;m going to stop pretending. Though ideas for New Horizons and Indigo are always brewing in my head, nothing&amp;rsquo;s happening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2021</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/april-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 01:48:57 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/april-2021/</guid>
      <description>Maintenance and Learning There are so many things that I was gonna write. But I got lazy and I got annoyed at how little I understand how Hugo, the software I use to generate this site, works. I would love to be able to create Table(s) of Contents, or add templates for things like signatures, or dynamically alter the font of the theme, but I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to do any of that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change of Schedule</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/change-of-schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 16:08:21 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/change-of-schedule/</guid>
      <description>No more weekly posts So I lied. Two weeks into my resolution and I&amp;rsquo;ve failed. The unfortunate reality is that some things take time to get right and sticking to a once per week schedule is too hard without sacrificing some depth and quality.
From this moment forth, the &amp;ldquo;on-schedule&amp;rdquo; post will be once every two weeks and all other timelines (i.e. posts with no timeline) will come whenever they are ready.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Site Who This</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/new-site-who-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 21:37:43 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/new-site-who-this/</guid>
      <description>Secret Hidden Level 1 Header This is my first post. Enjoy!
Part 1: Joke&amp;rsquo;s on you Joke&amp;rsquo;s on you, this isn&amp;rsquo;t my first rodeo with static site generators and as an experienced beginner level experimenter, I have a few complaints about static site generators.
I mean, why not have your first post be a complaint?
First, some history.
So, at one point in time at some point in time last year (2017) or so, I read somewhere that it was a great idea to showcase yourself by having a personal website as like a part-CV part experience point of reference.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
