<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on bananafish</title>
    <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on bananafish</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 12:21:57 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviewing the Moleskine Cahier</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/reviewing-the-moleskine-cahier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 00:46:36 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/reviewing-the-moleskine-cahier/</guid>
      <description>Cahier Journal  The Moleskine Cahiers are journels with a flexible heavy-duty cardboard cover in [colour] with visible stitching on the spine. The last 16 sheets are detachable and there is a pocket for loose notes. Each set of 2 pieces includes the Moleskine history.
 [Citation: above, as read by Google Assistant]
The reviews were sad. Literally sad. Ink bleeds through.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Te Wiki O Te Reo Māori</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/te-wiki-o-te-reo-maori/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 23:14:38 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/te-wiki-o-te-reo-maori/</guid>
      <description>Māori Language Week It&amp;rsquo;s Māori language week and since people are arguing over the language and it&amp;rsquo;s in the news again, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d weigh in on the debate if you can even call it that.
First, here&amp;rsquo;s a list of reasons people give not to learn Māori:
 It&amp;rsquo;s a dead dying language It&amp;rsquo;s a dead dying culture (Some idea of superiority) You get the idea  Secondly, I would like to say I&amp;rsquo;m a linguist, or to be more exact, I&amp;rsquo;m studying linguistics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Rust</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/learning-rust/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 17:13:05 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/learning-rust/</guid>
      <description>Fighting the borrow checker Anyone who has tried learning the Rust programming language will be familiar with the phrase &amp;ldquo;fighting the borrow checker&amp;rdquo;. It is the formative event in the Rust programmer&amp;rsquo;s life. Trying to figure out why the compiler won&amp;rsquo;t let you compile a piece of code. Those who use interpreted languages like Python and Ruby will not understand the pain of your code having to first successfully compile before being able to run it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modernity Has Failed Us</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/modernity-has-failed-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 21:50:30 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/modernity-has-failed-us/</guid>
      <description>A Brief Enquiry into Modern Society Last month, British band The 1975 released the second single from their upcoming album &amp;ldquo;A Brief Inquiry Into Online Relationships.&amp;rdquo; Barring being a good song, the song also functions as a good criticism of society as the album title denotes. The best line in my subjective opinion is &amp;ldquo;Oh! F*** your feelings! / Truth is only hearsay!&amp;rdquo; which highlights a critical problem in modern society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Use Fountain Pens</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/why-i-use-fountain-pens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 23:32:03 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/why-i-use-fountain-pens/</guid>
      <description>The rationale behind the use of antiquated writing instruments In an age of instantaneous interconnected digital communication and storage, one might wonder why another has a desire to use antiquated communication methods such as the pen and paper, especially a very antiquated breed of pen known only in the fringes of society and cautiously mentioned in everyday society as the fountain pen. If one looks at those proclaiming the dangers of technology and the benefits of digital detox, one will find a possible answer to the question at hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Site Who This</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/new-site-who-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 21:37:43 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/new-site-who-this/</guid>
      <description>Secret Hidden Level 1 Header This is my first post. Enjoy!
Part 1: Joke&amp;rsquo;s on you Joke&amp;rsquo;s on you, this isn&amp;rsquo;t my first rodeo with static site generators and as an experienced beginner level experimenter, I have a few complaints about static site generators.
I mean, why not have your first post be a complaint?
First, some history.
So, at one point in time at some point in time last year (2017) or so, I read somewhere that it was a great idea to showcase yourself by having a personal website as like a part-CV part experience point of reference.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>