<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on bananafish</title>
    <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on bananafish</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 12:21:57 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>reflections : introduction</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/reflections-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 13:17:57 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/reflections-introduction/</guid>
      <description>reflektioner (sv) I&amp;rsquo;m going to make a bold and untenable claim — I&amp;rsquo;m starting a series of reflections on various topics, ranging from stuff in my personal life to contemplation on the state of my various projects.
There&amp;rsquo;ll be no set release schedule; I think by now we all know I can&amp;rsquo;t stick to one. I&amp;rsquo;m making this series because I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing it a lot recently (in my head) : I&amp;rsquo;ve finished uni (I finally got a (casual) job) and I have no clue what I&amp;rsquo;m going to do in life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 in Review // Hopes for 2022</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/2021-in-review-hopes-for-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 02:25:16 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/2021-in-review-hopes-for-2022/</guid>
      <description>What better way to start off the new year than to review last year?
- Sebastian Lau, actually 2022 (actually 2021) Part 1: 2021 in Review Year of Stanisław Lem
The year of 2021 is declared the Year of Stanisław Lem in Poland, according to the November 27, 2020 resolution of Sejm (the lower house of the parliament of Poland). [...] 2021 is the year of the 100th Stanisław Lem anniversary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 2021</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/november-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 18:55:05 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/november-2021/</guid>
      <description>Preamble Isn&amp;rsquo;t ironic when you&amp;rsquo;re busy, you yearn for free time, but when you have lots of free time, you&amp;rsquo;re bored out of your mind?
No, just me?
November Update So, you may have noticed that my last post was in July; before that, the last post was in April. I managed to write enough to scrape by for the first four months.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a long year and I&amp;rsquo;ve forgotten most things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2021</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/july-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 02:27:39 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/july-2021/</guid>
      <description>The last post I made was in April.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to make an excuse; it&amp;rsquo;s a valid excuse. When May and June came around, so did all the assignments and coursework, and I was simply swamped by it all.
However, what&amp;rsquo;s not valid is using it not to work on my &amp;ldquo;projects&amp;rdquo;. They haven&amp;rsquo;t seen any progress in months (or years). For that reason, I&amp;rsquo;m going to stop pretending. Though ideas for New Horizons and Indigo are always brewing in my head, nothing&amp;rsquo;s happening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2021</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/april-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 01:48:57 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/april-2021/</guid>
      <description>Maintenance and Learning There are so many things that I was gonna write. But I got lazy and I got annoyed at how little I understand how Hugo, the software I use to generate this site, works. I would love to be able to create Table(s) of Contents, or add templates for things like signatures, or dynamically alter the font of the theme, but I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to do any of that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Haven&#39;t Been Writing</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/i-havent-been-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 12:31:50 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/i-havent-been-writing/</guid>
      <description>In the middle of January 2021 with nothing else to do, I made myself a New Years resolution. I vowed to write &amp;ldquo;once a week, or at the bare minimum, once a month&amp;rdquo;. I had a good run for three weeks in which I wrote a post roughly once a week. Then February hit, I procrastinated even more and the realisation that uni was looming sapped my willpower. So I amended my resolution to &amp;ldquo;once a fortnight&amp;rdquo; and wrote a single post in the entire month of February.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Price of Wisdom</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/the-price-of-wisdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 15:05:10 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/the-price-of-wisdom/</guid>
      <description>Goodbye, oh teeth of wisdom! So.., I had my wisdom teeth extracted. They caused more trouble than they were worth. One was growing into the tooth next to it whilst another failed to erupt and was stuck under the gum. My teeth were biting into the gums.
The biggest irony is that the tooth that should&amp;rsquo;ve caused trouble was perfectly fine and the one that should&amp;rsquo;ve been fine was causing infections and swelling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change of Schedule</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/change-of-schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 16:08:21 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/change-of-schedule/</guid>
      <description>No more weekly posts So I lied. Two weeks into my resolution and I&amp;rsquo;ve failed. The unfortunate reality is that some things take time to get right and sticking to a once per week schedule is too hard without sacrificing some depth and quality.
From this moment forth, the &amp;ldquo;on-schedule&amp;rdquo; post will be once every two weeks and all other timelines (i.e. posts with no timeline) will come whenever they are ready.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indecision and Imitation</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/indecision-and-imitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 13:11:46 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/indecision-and-imitation/</guid>
      <description>Creativity + a small announcement We are often told that &amp;ldquo;imitation is the best form of flattery&amp;rdquo; as a commandment to instead seek originality. However, our greatest works do not exist in a vacuum, they revisit and reinterpret existing ideas in subtle ways and inspire thought. Of course, counterfeits, piracy and copyright infringement are huge issues.
Voltaire (once) said, &amp;ldquo;Ainsi, presque tout est imitation&amp;hellip; Les esprits les plus originaux empruntent les uns des autres,&amp;rdquo; or artistically rendered:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Year 2021</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/a-new-year-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:30:30 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/a-new-year-2021/</guid>
      <description>Jan 17, 2021 Blah, blah, blah, 2020 was a terrible year. Done.
In the never-ending spirit tradition of setting a new year&amp;rsquo;s resolution that we don&amp;rsquo;t keep to, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d set a resolution given that we&amp;rsquo;re still in the opening days of the new year, i.e. it&amp;rsquo;s still January. I&amp;rsquo;ve still got time to start&amp;hellip;
 I promise to write at least one post per fortnight, or at the bare minimum, once a month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Justice</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/social-justice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 23:06:40 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/social-justice/</guid>
      <description>First published on Genesis Planetary on 24 Jun 2017.
[This is a work of fiction. Names, characters, businesses, places, events and incidents are either the products of the author’s imagination or used in a fictitious manner. Any resemblance to actual persons, living or dead, or actual events is purely coincidental.]
The city was filled endlessly with these streets. Wide-built, marked by a row of towering commercial buildings on each side, most of them dilapidated or on the verge of becoming heritage sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Site Who This</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/new-site-who-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 21:37:43 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/new-site-who-this/</guid>
      <description>Secret Hidden Level 1 Header This is my first post. Enjoy!
Part 1: Joke&amp;rsquo;s on you Joke&amp;rsquo;s on you, this isn&amp;rsquo;t my first rodeo with static site generators and as an experienced beginner level experimenter, I have a few complaints about static site generators.
I mean, why not have your first post be a complaint?
First, some history.
So, at one point in time at some point in time last year (2017) or so, I read somewhere that it was a great idea to showcase yourself by having a personal website as like a part-CV part experience point of reference.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
