<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>projects on bananafish</title>
    <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/tags/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in projects on bananafish</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 18:55:05 +1300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://le-bananafish.github.io/tags/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>November 2021</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/november-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 18:55:05 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/november-2021/</guid>
      <description>Preamble Isn&amp;rsquo;t ironic when you&amp;rsquo;re busy, you yearn for free time, but when you have lots of free time, you&amp;rsquo;re bored out of your mind?
No, just me?
November Update So, you may have noticed that my last post was in July; before that, the last post was in April. I managed to write enough to scrape by for the first four months.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a long year and I&amp;rsquo;ve forgotten most things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2021</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/july-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 02:27:39 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/july-2021/</guid>
      <description>The last post I made was in April.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to make an excuse; it&amp;rsquo;s a valid excuse. When May and June came around, so did all the assignments and coursework, and I was simply swamped by it all.
However, what&amp;rsquo;s not valid is using it not to work on my &amp;ldquo;projects&amp;rdquo;. They haven&amp;rsquo;t seen any progress in months (or years). For that reason, I&amp;rsquo;m going to stop pretending. Though ideas for New Horizons and Indigo are always brewing in my head, nothing&amp;rsquo;s happening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indecision and Imitation</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/indecision-and-imitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 13:11:46 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/indecision-and-imitation/</guid>
      <description>Creativity + a small announcement We are often told that &amp;ldquo;imitation is the best form of flattery&amp;rdquo; as a commandment to instead seek originality. However, our greatest works do not exist in a vacuum, they revisit and reinterpret existing ideas in subtle ways and inspire thought. Of course, counterfeits, piracy and copyright infringement are huge issues.
Voltaire (once) said, &amp;ldquo;Ainsi, presque tout est imitation&amp;hellip; Les esprits les plus originaux empruntent les uns des autres,&amp;rdquo; or artistically rendered:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Justice</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/social-justice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 23:06:40 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/social-justice/</guid>
      <description>First published on Genesis Planetary on 24 Jun 2017.
[This is a work of fiction. Names, characters, businesses, places, events and incidents are either the products of the author’s imagination or used in a fictitious manner. Any resemblance to actual persons, living or dead, or actual events is purely coincidental.]
The city was filled endlessly with these streets. Wide-built, marked by a row of towering commercial buildings on each side, most of them dilapidated or on the verge of becoming heritage sites.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
