<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reflections on bananafish</title>
    <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/tags/reflections/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reflections on bananafish</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-NZ</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 02:20:42 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://le-bananafish.github.io/tags/reflections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2023 in Review</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/2023-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 02:20:42 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/2023-in-review/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt;&amp;gt; This post is super late.&#xA;I set myself the lofty goal to &amp;ldquo;write&amp;rdquo; and work on my creative projects more this year and you can see from the dearth of posts (this is only the second one1) that I have not succeeded. In my defence, I chose to do a postgraduate degree (honours).&#xA;I was not mentally prepared for that endeavour.&#xA;Having finished four and a half years of study in semester 1 of 2022, I intended to take the second half of the year off but ended up working part-time and I fell out of the mindset of a student: the pressure of deadlines, the anxiety of rushing between classes, all of that faded away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2023</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:41:43 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/2023/</guid>
      <description>Twenty twenty-three will be the year I stop putting too much pressure on myself.&#xA;2023 is the year that I will do the things that I want to do in life.&#xA;Last year was a year of great change and paralysis. It was the year in which I finished my undergraduate degree(s) and the question of what I truly wanted to do in the future stared me straight in the face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>reflections : introduction</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/reflections-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 13:17:57 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/reflections-introduction/</guid>
      <description>reflektioner (sv)&amp;nbsp;¶ I&amp;rsquo;m going to make a bold and untenable claim — I&amp;rsquo;m starting a series of reflections on various topics, ranging from stuff in my personal life to contemplation on the state of my various projects.&#xA;There&amp;rsquo;ll be no set release schedule; I think by now we all know I can&amp;rsquo;t stick to one. I&amp;rsquo;m making this series because I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing it a lot recently (in my head) : I&amp;rsquo;ve finished uni (I finally got a (casual) job) and I have no clue what I&amp;rsquo;m going to do in life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2021 in Review // Hopes for 2022</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/2021-in-review-hopes-for-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 02:25:16 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/2021-in-review-hopes-for-2022/</guid>
      <description>What better way to start off the new year than to review last year? - Sebastian Lau, actually 2022 (actually 2021)&#xA;Part 1: 2021 in Review&amp;nbsp;¶ Year of Stanisław Lem&amp;nbsp;¶ The year of 2021 is declared the Year of Stanisław Lem in Poland, according to the November 27, 2020 resolution of Sejm (the lower house of the parliament of Poland). [&amp;hellip;] 2021 is the year of the 100th Stanisław Lem anniversary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>November 2021</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/november-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 18:55:05 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/november-2021/</guid>
      <description>Preamble&amp;nbsp;¶ Isn&amp;rsquo;t ironic when you&amp;rsquo;re busy, you yearn for free time, but when you have lots of free time, you&amp;rsquo;re bored out of your mind?&#xA;No, just me?&#xA;November Update&amp;nbsp;¶ So, you may have noticed that my last post was in July; before that, the last post was in April. I managed to write enough to scrape by for the first four months.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s been a long year and I&amp;rsquo;ve forgotten most things.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Year 2021</title>
      <link>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/a-new-year-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:30:30 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://le-bananafish.github.io/posts/a-new-year-2021/</guid>
      <description>Jan 17, 2021&amp;nbsp;¶ Blah, blah, blah, 2020 was a terrible year. Done.&#xA;In the never-ending spirit tradition of setting a new year&amp;rsquo;s resolution that we don&amp;rsquo;t keep to, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d set a resolution given that we&amp;rsquo;re still in the opening days of the new year, i.e. it&amp;rsquo;s still January. I&amp;rsquo;ve still got time to start&amp;hellip;&#xA;I promise to write at least one post per fortnight, or at the bare minimum, once a month.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
